[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie 8 Mile B-Rabbit decides to go to the Shelter again. He beats Lickety Split and Lotto. Who did he win against in the third tournament?", "correct_answer": "Papa Doc", "incorrect_answers": ["Wink", "DJ Iz", "Lil Tic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country will you find the impressive Neuschwanstein Castle, which was the inspiration for Sleeping Beauty Castle at Disneyland Park?", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Denmark", "Austria", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor from the TV series Lost had a role in the 2004 Crash?", "correct_answer": "Daniel Dae Kim", "incorrect_answers": ["Matthew Fox", "Jorge Garcia", "Terry OQuinn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This amendment of the United States Constitution, which is part of the Bill of Rights, guards against unreasonable searches and seizures.", "correct_answer": "Fourth Amendment", "incorrect_answers": ["Fifth Amendment", "Sixth Amendment", "Third Amendment"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first centerfold of Playboy magazine?", "correct_answer": "Marilyn Monroe", "incorrect_answers": ["Bette Paige", "Joan Crawford", "Jayne Mansfield"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the following medications are contraindicated during pregnancy, EXCEPT which one?", "correct_answer": "Nitrofurantoin", "incorrect_answers": ["Tetracycline", "Valproic Acid", "Methotrexate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of the nicknames of the characters in the movie American Pie?", "correct_answer": "Wally", "incorrect_answers": ["Oz", "Finch", "Stifler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fictional dinosaur-inhabited island Isla Nublar from the 1993 movie Jurassic Park is located close to this country.", "correct_answer": "Costa Rica", "incorrect_answers": ["The Philippines", "Cuba", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These agents are used to transport active ingredients through the skin and take them where they would be most effective.", "correct_answer": "Nanosomes", "incorrect_answers": ["UV", "Ceramides", "THC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average lifespan of a vampire bat?", "correct_answer": "40-50 years", "incorrect_answers": ["20-25 years", "5-10 years", "70-80 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many cubs are usually in a tigers litter?", "correct_answer": "3-4 cubs", "incorrect_answers": ["1-6 cubs", "1-2 cubs", "2-4 cubs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the novel Young Lions which was adapted into a movie starring Marlon Brando, Montgomery Clift, and Dean Martin?", "correct_answer": "Irwin Shaw", "incorrect_answers": ["Theodore Dreiser", "Truman Capote", "Norman Mailer"]}]